every
made
The One who
on
words
two
ocean gasped
cross:
a
thirst.
I
twenty-two.
Psalm
it in the
wrote
David
person,
first
someone
picturing
but he was
death.
else's
give out:
body
Watch the
up
is dried
"My strength
a potsherd;
like
to
cleaveth
and my tongue
jaws;
my
brought me
hast
and thou
death."
the dust of
into
clay;
Dried
fast;
stuck
a tongue
the
sinking into
man
a
of death.
dust
the dying
records
Then John
cry:
Jesus'
thirst."
"I
foretell that
doesn't
twenty-two
Psalm
cry
behind
thirst
it paints the
it,
before He
years
a thousand
it.
felt
thirsting:
is
And think who
who made every
One
the
and spring,
river
living
world
who offers the
water
with nothing,
there
hanging
place.
in your
dry so that
went
He
never
drink and
you could
again.
thirst
who made every
God
The
thirst
cried out in
ocean
you
hand
so He could
that never
water
the one
fails.
is Himself.
water
And that